Okay, great. Okay, then Darlings, welcome to another one of my goal set and
workshops.
And I hope this is good as the others, because I feel like a lot of the time
the girls say,
especially Sami, how much they love these calls, so I hope that I do them
justice today.
So yeah, let's get started, shall we? So I'm just going to share my screen.
I'm going sorry one moment, I just need to allow it to be able to be done.
The person I've done this on this new laptop, sorry, I just need to unlock it.
Okay. Okay, can you see my screen now? Great. I didn't think it was going to
allow me to
do that before, so I'm just going to have to restart the laptop. Okay, great.
So everyone
can see the PowerPoint. Yes, okay, perfect. So goal setting workshop.
If you fail to prepare, you prepare to fail. Very simple, easy saying, but
super true at
the same time. So today, we'll get some preparation involved. So yeah, we can
be on track to achieving
our goals. Firstly, I would like to talk about the autumn equinox. Is that how
it's said
well, or is it equinox, would you say? Okay, okay, okay, so the autumn equinox.
So the
autumn equinox is actually this Friday. And what it is, it's when the sun is
directly
above the equator and day and night are at equal lengths. And it also marks the
beginning
of autumn. Traditionally, the autumn equinox was the time to honour the harvest.
The farmers
would harvest their crops and get them ready to be used in the colder months.
Metaphorically,
it refers to the harvest of goals and intentions you set or planned or planted
when the years
started, and how those goals have been evolving or growing. So I think this is
a good time.
Sorry, to show some self appreciation. So what we can do is so we can look back
at some
of the goals that we set at the start of the year. We can maybe think of at
least one goal
that we wanted to achieve and give thanks to ourselves for achieving that goal
or for
being on our way to achieve it and to feel grateful for everything achieved
this year
and to be proud of ourselves. So I think that this is a nice exercise to start
on just to
get us into a good mindset. So maybe we can all, because now it's obviously the
ninth
month of the year, so we can all take a look back at the start of the year and
think if
there was something that we've decided we wanted to achieve and then have a
little think
about, you know, if we've done it or how close we are to doing it. And yeah,
just give thanks
to ourselves for achieving this. And maybe we can all share if you would like
to. So
I'll give us a moment to think about that one. Okay, so I'll share one of mine
first
and then maybe somebody else would like to share with us. So one of my goals
this year
was to learn how to do fire dance and how to perform with fire. And yeah, that
was something
that I wanted to achieve. And to be honest, when I started it, I just didn't
think that
I would probably get as good as I did or, you know, do some of the things that
I've already
done. And yeah, it's nice now to look back on that and feel proud that I've
achieved
that because then it makes me feel better to then go on and do more and do
whatever
else I can then go and do, you know. So yes, does anybody else want to share
something
maybe they've achieved this year? Sami, are you trying to unmute yourself there
?
Did you hear me? Yes. So I've got a few things. One of them is moving into this
beautiful
house that I'm almost certain that I've manifested for myself. And yeah, it's
like my dream home
and at the start of the year, I did a vision ball just one of our exercises.
And one of
the things I did was write about the kind of house that I wanted and how I
wanted it
to be and I wanted to achieve moving into this sort of forever home, which I've
done.
So I'm really pleased about that. And I booked and went to my booth this year
and I'm booked
to go to Disneyland with how in, we've just had to move it back because I've
passed but
didn't arrive in time. But to an event in November, and then two of the things
that
I wanted to achieve as well. So I've achieved quite a lot, really, so far.
Yeah, it's and Sami. So proud of you. I've achieved that. Amazing. That must
feel good.
You've got your house, you've got your holidays. Especially the house, because
that's like
a really big goal. And, you know, to manifest that. And last year, if you test
me out this
time next year, you're going to move that you're going to live in this
beautiful house. It's
going to be like a dream and it's going to be like a forever home. And I would
have been
like, oh, no, that seems too much. But I just manifested the shit out of it.
And I've got
it. And I'm so grateful for it. It's just amazing. So it does work.
Definitely. That's amazing, Sami. Thank you for sharing that.
You feel emotional. It's lovely, Sami. Thank you. You're welcome.
Does anyone else want to share? No. Oh, yes. Go on, we are now. Yeah, you're
unmuted.
I don't know how to change it. We can hear you, by the way. Oh, you can hear me
? Yes.
Okay. I left a really toxic job situation that I've worked in for years. And I
just
knew how unhealthy and how unhappy it was making me. And I quit. And now I've
like basically
I was working nights for absolute years. And it's been a really hard transition
getting
myself into daytime mode. But now I like wake up at 6am or 7am. And that's
something I've
wanted for years. And I just haven't been able to do that. That's when I used
to go to bed.
And I paid off like pretty much all of my debts that I had as well. There's
like only
like a little bit of one left. And yeah, I mean, other things as well. I've
been working
on healing my heart and all of that stuff. But yeah. That's amazing. Really,
really amazing.
It seems like you've really changed your life around, you know, like completely
changed
your goal and paying off your debt and stuff like that. And healing your heart
so sweet.
I love that. That's amazing. Thank you for sharing. Yeah. Anybody else want to
share
before we move on? Oh, I think I'll run around. So one of my goals at the start
of the year,
which was like a long term goal was to be a counseling supervisor. So to like
take the
next step up with that. And I was going to start a course in September, but I
decided
to push myself, which I regretted many times and did do the course. I started
in January.
So I did it over the summer. So I just finished it in August. And it's quite
fitting because
I literally just spoke to my first counselor client today. So yeah, I didn't
expect that
I would have done that next step just yet with the summer holidays and
everything else.
But I'm really happy that half. So yeah, nice. Amazing to you. Thank you for
sharing.
Like, yeah, I'm so proud of you for that. I knew you'd smash a day. So yeah,
well done,
darling. Okay, then we'll move on. Then if nobody else would like to share it.
The shot
of Charlotte's put in the child's as well. Ah, yes. Okay. Thank you. I didn't
see that.
Okay. So Nadia wrote, I'm proud that I've been able to get into such a good
headspace
mentally, letting to remove negative people from my life, even family. You know
what,
I think that's so important because this is something that we think of just
because
the family or just because the close friends I've known them all this time, you
know, we
would allow them into like, allow them still in our lives, even if they're not
treating
us right. And like, that's not how it should be, you know, not even, not even
blood. If
you're not adding or to some, you know, if someone's not adding to your life,
they're
just taking, taking, taking all the time. Then, yeah, you need to be evaluated
doing
yourself. Well done, Nadia. That's not the easiest thing to do, but good for
you. And
Charlotte wrote, I registered to start my PhD in a couple of weeks, which I've
been working
towards for a year now and felt almost impossible just a few months ago. So it
feels like a
huge milestone. Oh, that's beautiful. Charlotte, that's so lovely. That's like,
I get goosebumps
and reading that. That's amazing. So yeah, good for you, girl. Clever clogs.
Okay, amazing.
Thank you, girlies, for all sharing. Okay, let's head on to the next slide.
Okay, so
now that we're all in a beautiful mindset, let's get started on setting some
goals. Okay,
exercise one. First of all, I'd like you all to list every single goal you want
to achieve
the big ones, the small ones, the unimaginable ones, the ones that's going to
take years,
the ones that could take you five minutes, just write them all on the page and
just empty
your mind. Got about five minutes to do this. I've done this one before on most
of these
calls, and I like to start with this because I think it's good to just empty
your mind
on the page, and then we can think more clearly when we speak about individual
goals. So let's
just write down everything we want to achieve and I'll set a timer now. I'll
give us a couple
of minutes to do this. I'm going to do it alongside you as well.
Put on a bit of meditation music to help us all write in all of the things.
[Music], and then we'll do the next one. So let's go. [Music], and then we'll
do the next one.
[Music], and then we'll do the next one.
Maybe stuff that you've been putting off, stuff like that.
Okay then, and how's everyone getting on? Do we need more time, or does
everyone doing okay?
And see some people are still right, and so I'll give us another moment, and
then we'll head on to the next part of the exercise.
And you can always go back at the end as well, and if you felt like there wasn
't enough time to complete each one, you can always go back and go over it again
at the end when we finish.
Okay, so now we're going to go through and label these goals with one week, two
weeks, one month, three months, six months, or one year, or two years, five
years, whatever.
Give yourself a time frame from what you're going to set yourself to achieve
each goal. So for example, one of my goals is edit a video, and I'm going to
give myself a week to get that done.
And another one, for example, is save up a certain amount of money, and I'm
going to give myself a year to get that one done so just go through and just
realistically work out how long it could take yourself to achieve each one and
just write that next to your goal.
The mind could take me one week and if not being done it's like now I'm looking
at it I'm like just going to get it done now.
It would have been sat on my list for weeks and weeks.
So, I'm going to go through and make sure that I'm done.
Okay.
If you're not finished just by now you can always go back through later on.
So, now we're going to go and pick one to three of the one week goals that you
can get done this week.
So obviously if you've got a couple of little ones that you can do all in one
week you can pick a few of them, or if there's one that could take you like the
whole week and just pick that one.
So, I'll just go back and pick one to three of them that you can get done this
week, and you know just make that clear highlight them.
Okay.
Now, for the one week goals the ones that we're going to get done within a week
so if you've only picked one of them, or if you picked two or three of them.
So, by Wednesday, the 28th of October. Oh, it's not open is it?
It's September. Let's just say let's just act like that says September. So, by
Wednesday the 28th of September, I will have achieved or I will have done and
then write out whatever it is that you need to do, because it's actually a fact
that if you've written out in your own right
and that you're going to do something, you're a lot more likely to actually get
it done so even all is just writing this now is in going to be one little thing
that we can do to put it in the right direction to actually do it.
So, by Wednesday the 28th of September.
Okay.
[Music]
Okay. Would anyone like to share what they've written out by Wednesday the 28th
of November?
I was about to say, God, I've got no clue what month we're in. Would anyone
like to share with Jim what statement they've made for what they would like to
achieve within the week?
I'll start off with sharing mine and maybe someone else will want to share. So,
by Wednesday the 28th of September, I will have edited and uploaded both new
videos to YouTube for the welcome course for the welcome call, which I've been
working on today but I've still got one more to do.
I will have done six reels for my Instagram and I will have made and edited new
content for my website.
So, yes, and it actually felt good to write that down to say it because there's
been one of those things that I've actually kept off, kept on back for so long,
and to know that I'm going to have it done, you know, by next week, it feels
good because it's like, yes, that's going to be gone now, it's all going to be
done and I'm going to feel a lot lighter, but a lot less to do.
So yeah, it feels good even writing it and saying it. So yes, does anybody else
want to share?
I think we both did that at the same time.
I didn't have any weekly ones, I think I wrote loads of like big goals, but
then I thought, even if they're big goals, I can still do things in one week
towards that big goal.
I broke down three of my big goals and said, by Wednesday, the 28th of
September, I will have written at least one chapter for my book.
I've had five natural hair days because I'm trying to like get my natural hair
back and grow it, and I've had one successful supervision session so my new
client will be starting.
My big goal is to have like a successful practice of that but yeah, trying to
break them down into little things.
That's amazing, I love that well, absolutely love that. Thank you for sharing.
And your natural hair is absolutely beautiful, it looks so good right now and
that's natural right, that's your natural hair tie back.
Yeah, it looks lovely.
Yeah, it looks gorgeous.
Yeah, so yeah, you can't make the video but as well.
Do you want to share Sammy?
Yeah, so I did a bit like well, I had big goals, so I broke them down a little
bit so I put by Wednesday the 28th of September, I would have achieved these
goals and they were to book in.
I placed just up my mum's some yoga sessions because they've got like a studio
just up the road on her farm.
And me and my sister keep saying that we're going to go every week, but we
haven't.
So I want to have it like book like six weeks booked and done so that's like a
six week sort of plan but I want to have it booked and done by next week.
Yeah, I want to do some work on my profile for work because I haven't updated
it recently.
And I think September is like most people reset and restart in January,
September is kind of like that for me.
Because after like the summer, the kids go back to school and stuff like that.
So after like, not being a routine for work and having quite a lot of time off
or just sitting in can, you know, sort of when I could.
I really got out of routine. So I want to get back into a really good routine,
a daytime routine as well because obviously I can full time.
And I've just got really out of actually putting in full time hours, which I
used to always do.
So I want to buy next week.
I want to have like a proper rotor or not rotor, but you know what I mean, like
a proper routine sort of structured plan of what times we're going to go on
each day I want to stick to it.
And had that all written down and had like my profile edited and updated a bit
because I think if you do that, and then start a new routine it always works
for me anyway.
Yeah, so then my two sort of broken down goals.
Amazing.
I think sitting down and biting it out and thinking about what works for you,
like, especially if you've got kids or even if you haven't got kids and you've
got other commitments or another job or whatever, just sitting down and work.
I'm thinking about like realistically what can I do, what can I give this, you
know, it's easy to say I want to log on from like nine till two every day where
the kids are at school but sometimes you know you have other stuff to do as
well.
So I think that realistically sitting down and then sticking to like a certain
amount of time each day that works for you and feels good for you. It's so
worthwhile.
Totally.
Yeah, I want to do that. Yeah.
Amazing. Well, thank you for sharing. Yeah.
Oh, Charlotte just said she has to just rush off. Okay. Okay. Did anyone else
want to share before we move on.
No. Yeah. No. Okay.
Okay, then let's head to the next exercise.
Okay, so exercise to.
Okay, so now we're going to choose one of our year goals.
So the ones that we said will take us up to be here. I'm going to use the grow
model to help us achieve this.
Okay, so the grow model. So it stands for goal reality options and will.
Basically stands for you know what is your goal. What is it that you want to do
.
Reality is so where are you now.
And what are some of the barriers that I may be maybe preventing you from
achieving this goal.
And also think as well if there are any limiting beliefs or any mental blocks
that are getting in your way of you achieving this.
And then we've got options.
So what could you do. What can you do right now to get you on the way to
achieving your goal. What resources do you have available to you.
And what changes can you make to your own behaviour. You know what barriers can
you overcome.
And how are you going to go about achieving this.
So yeah, just unless one you can have a little think like of all the different
options and all different ways you can go about achieving this goal.
And finally will. So what are you actually going to do like what are you going
to do right now to start to achieve this.
When are you going to start and yeah when do you plan to have this done by.
So I'm going to give you five minutes to do this. So just choose one of the
bigger goals so one of your year ones or even one of your month ones or three
month ones, whatever one you feel to.
You can always go back after this and do it for your other goals and I'm just
used to grow my goal to break it down.
So I'll just read out again what the stand for so goal, what you want to do
like what is the ultimate goal reality.
So where are you now. What are some of the barriers preventing you from
achieving your goal.
So are there anything any limiting beliefs or mental blocks that are getting in
the way.
Options, what could you do what resources are available to you. What changes
can you make to your own behaviour to overcome some barriers.
So you thought about the barriers before that we're there. What can you do to
overcome this and let go of this.
Generally will. What will you do to get on track to achieving this what changes
can you make when can you start working on it and when when will this be done
by.
[Music]
Obviously we've written out that we've broken down you know what we want where
we are with regards to a close we are to achieving it or what.
And we've wrote down a lot of options we've got to achieve in it and then also
what we're going to do.
I think now it would be good and to just maybe on the bit with you know the
very end one on will what we're going to do.
Right down a date when we're going to actually start this because I've done
this on one of the calls a while ago because I've seen somewhere online I've
something about this about writing a start date.
And it's said about you know because we've all got those to do lists that just
stay the same for a long time.
And I felt like that was a personal attack on me because this is me sometimes I
have a list on my phone of stuff that I should have done so long ago.
And then I went through and I'm going to start it on this date and then I did I
got it started and then before a new year.
It was just easy piecing it was all done so yeah I think sometimes you know we
can get carried away with just procrastinating on these things.
So let's all write down when we're going to get started on whatever it is to
start to achieve in this goal.
Okay, great.
Did anyone want to share any of their one year goals or their bigger goals
before we move on.
And I just thought I'd say because and you mentioned this to me briefly didn't
you the other day this like this grow model which I've never heard of before.
And I think it's really good. And when you said about will, I think I sort of
like talking in a different way. So when I did like the exercise as you said,
and ready to start dating everything.
And I also thought about well as in willpower, because I thought, well my
willpower and I thought what is going to give me the willpower like where I'm
going to get the will from to do it.
Now write down like some stuff that, you know, how I'd feel what I'd get and
what would happen if I got it's trending the willpower to do it as well.
Definitely I like that. Yeah, because then if you know how you're going to feel
when you when you've done it then you're more likely to want to do it on you.
So yeah, amazing. Thank you to yeah. Okay then.
So moving on.
So I thought we would end with some money mindset stuff because when we were
planning this call and when I mentioned about planning this a couple of the
girls mentioned in the group that they would like something on this so I
thought I'd end on a little bit with money mindset.
Okay, so couple of bullet points I'd like to discuss and then if anyone else
has got any, you know, anything they like to do to get themselves in a good
mindset about money, please share because the more the matter really.
So look at the bigger picture. So these, these first two actually in all these
first couple actually come from relevant content credit for this. She told me
these the other day on what's up when I was speaking to about this.
So yeah I thought it was really good so I added them into the into the
PowerPoint.
So look at the bigger picture so sometimes.
If you're feeling down about money, you know, it can kind of consume how you
feel about everything because it can feel like.
Yeah, it can feel overwhelmed and counted sometimes and if we just step back
and look at the bigger picture sometimes and think, well, actually, I've got a
roof over my head.
I've got food in my table. I've got water coming up the top. I've got a bed,
you know, I've got this laptop that allows me to be able to make money and, you
know, like we can, I'm sure we can all think of so many things.
That we could be grateful for and actually stepping back and looking at the
bigger picture.
Might help us to reframe our mindset together into a positive mindset and then,
you know, the better our mindset is in about life, the better it's going to be
about money.
So yeah, that's what I take on looking at the bigger picture but maybe you'll
take something different from there.
I think that's something good to do.
And also, you can check what money you've got coming in. So, for example, if
you know you've got a regular wage that comes in, or, you know, if you have so
many clients booked in for next week and you know how much you're going to get
paid for each client.
You can wear how much you've got coming in and that can make you feel a bit
better.
If you're not feeling so good about money and you feel like you're lacking, and
then you think, oh well actually, I've got 600 pound coming in next week so,
you know, you can think oh yeah actually I'm not doing as bad as I thought.
So yeah for that was a good little good one you could do. Well I didn't think
that that was well.
And I miss over one that we've done before me and well was to withdraw some
cash and keep it in your purse.
So you can withdraw like 50 or 100 pound and keep it in your purse and don't
spend it.
And when you're out and about, you can, you know, see things that cost that
amount of money or whatever else and just know that if you really wanted to you
could have those things.
So I feel like this one is good for like yeah just getting your back into a
better mindset about money instead of thinking, I couldn't have that, you know
you've got the money there to have it whether you're going to go and get it or
not.
You know, it's him. Yeah, and I think just having money on yet just.
Yeah, I don't know if you're like it's just going to attract more to yeah I
feel.
And then also noticing limiting beliefs. So I mentioned this before.
This is a huge one I feel for a lot of people because you know.
Well it definitely was for me and whenever I feel like I'm lacking a lack of
money it's only whenever I'm feeling worse about it and then I feel like I get
more and more situations that come.
That make me feel bad about money so, and it's all it's all to do with how I'm
feeling and you know what my beliefs are about money in that moment.
So, and if you've got like any limiting beliefs about money, you can actually
do some, some rituals to let them go like this is what I do sometimes so,
especially on the full moon it's good to do rituals of letting go on the full
moon because it's almost like
we're letting go of as the former change into its new quarter. It's in like you
know it's changing its rebirth you can let go of the old beliefs old intentions
and welcoming some new positive ones.
So what you can actually do is it's something I've done before, you can even
write out on a bit of paper all of your negative limiting beliefs about money
or about anything it doesn't need to be just about money.
I see we're talking about money mindset right now but this goes for everything
can write out all of your limiting beliefs on a piece of paper, maybe on the
foremoon or just whenever you're feeling it you know whenever you're feeling.
So feel it's all about just intention and how you're feeling to, and then you
can just ban it and just let it go into the universe and fly away and just don
't let it back in.
And yeah, I think maybe that's a little exercise you could do.
Obviously it's not as easy to sometimes but just doing little rituals like this
will just help to just changing your mindset.
I feel anyway.
And never tell yourself you can't have something.
So I feel like it's so easy to say, I'd never be able to afford that or I'd
never be able to have this. And it's like, well if you're telling yourself that
, then you definitely won't because if you don't even believe it yourself, and
how are you ever going to have it because no one's going to just go out there
and hand it to you.
Well, very, very unlikely. So if you yourself believe you're not going to have
it then probably never going to but if you think you know what, one day I could
have this stuff. Yeah, I will have that one day.
Then you've opened the possibility to having it and you're allowing yourself to
actually go through it rather than just shutting it off.
So yeah, this is something when I hear people around me saying stuff like this,
and I just want to slap it off and be like no, don't say that like because you
know then you're never going to have it.
Okay, and finally, it's kind of linking on from the last one, believe you
deserve it, because we do, we do deserve it and we deserve whatever whatever we
want really, and there's no limit on what we can have in every believer.
So yeah, they're my few little money mindset tips. Does anybody else have any
money mindset tips you want to share.
Hello, sorry, can I go on, go on, yeah.
Is that right, just, just picking up on what you just said about, you know,
saying that you deserve it.
Like, I think that's so important, I believe in that you deserve something like
when I moved into this home, and you know like I felt really lucky and I was
like, oh my God, and so many people said to me I was telling you really deserve
this.
Like you so deserve it, like, if people get signed to me or you deserve it you
deserve it and then I think, do you know what yeah I do deserve it I do bloody
deserve to have this you know what I mean so just that mindset of actually
believing that you deserve something.
I think is quite a powerful thing and yeah, we all deserve whatever we desire
really so yeah I think that's quite an important thing to remember.
Yeah, definitely. Thank you Sammy. I completely agree.
That's right.
Yeah, I used to be someone who told myself these things like, no, I didn't
deserve this or can never have this or this or that and I did never have the
things that I wanted.
But I feel like since I changed my mindset, I know I could have anything and
achieve anything that I want.
Yeah, no matter what background you come from or if you're privileged or not
privileged or you've had certain things that have happened to you in your life
that have been bad or good.
We all deserve, you know, what we put in, we should get back and we do deserve
good things if which we all are good people so I think that's important if you
keep on a high sort of vibe and a high energy with people around yourself with
people that bring you up and not down.
You're always going to, you know, be happier and be more abundant.
Yeah, definitely like, and it's one of them of course we have moments of like,
you know, where we doubt ourselves and we get into this and that and that's
totally normal and that's totally okay but then try and reframe that and get
yourself back into the good mindset as soon as you can.
But yeah, thank you Sammy.
Okay then ladies, we've come to the end now does anyone want to share anything
before we leave.
I want to share something just, I can't remember exactly what it was now so I
thought I was listening to this audio book yesterday.
And that's a good thing as well, like for money mindset listening to like I
would never listen to this type of thing normally but I listened to an audio
book about how to get rich.
And I just had it playing in the background while I was doing things in the
house to do my jobs and stuff.
And one of the things that said what that like stage of me a bit was that we
always have to be bigger than the place we're in now.
And it really stayed with me because I thought that's what I've done every time
I've like leveled up in my life, you know, so come from nothing.
I've had times where I thought I've never come out of this place where I'm in,
but then I've been bigger than the place I'm in. So, so I've had like bigger
ideas.
And I thought what possible or I've like had, you know, spoke to a bigger
audience then is directly here or just always thought bigger than the place I'm
in right now.
But it feels a nice like mindset change and way to think like always just
thinking bigger even though you're not there yet just thinking about the bigger
thing acting as if it was already there.
No.
Yeah, definitely I like that I really like that. And that made me think as well
like yeah true I need to think bigger.
So yeah, thank you for sharing.
Oh dear. Yeah. I actually wanted to ask for some tips of you guys, because I
always feel that I log on to come way later than I really want to like I set
myself a time I want to be online and then I don't end up going on and it's
obviously like a motivation thing.
I always get like this extreme anxiety before I log on, and then it just like
stops me from like logging on for ages. And once I'm on and I'm getting calls I
feel fine, but it's just like that jump I just don't know.
I have to get used to doing it properly again. But I don't know like is that
anything you guys would recommend for me to just be able to get my ass online,
like as quick as possible.
Do you have a routine like do you have a routine that you do maybe you could
switch up your routine so it's more pleasurable so it's less like I'm going to
work now more fun.
Maybe that I find that I've been doing going into the free chat quite when I do
work I do go into the free chat quite a lot because I find that that really
gets the callers in.
But then I find it quite draining. So I think maybe because I'm like in my mind
I'm thinking oh I'm going into the free chat and instantly I know have to talk
to people.
And that also like stresses me out. I don't know.
Have you tried not doing that for a little while. I didn't do it today I logged
on for maybe like an hour earlier and I didn't go into the free chat and I had
one of my regulars called me.
And he's going to be calling me back later on when I log back online.
And how did you feel about that today log on know and that you wasn't going on
free chat that make you feel better about it. And did you get on.
Yeah, because I tried to go on last night and I went into the free chat and
then I didn't stay on for very long so I was like no.
And I just logged out.
It's so hard having to meet all the time.
Yeah, like I find it really draining and I know that it works really well for
some girls, but I just can't do it and it does it stresses me out.
It makes me anxious. I feel like it puts me in a bad mood and I don't want to
continue working.
It just really doesn't work for me at all. And it doesn't make, I don't have my
full potential I don't think because as soon as someone then does want to talk
to me I'm exhausted but I'm annoyed.
And it's like I'm not, I just think, at least someone's now paying. Like, you
know what I mean like it's that kind of attitude which is I don't think is a
good attitude to start with.
I really have that energy last night. Yeah, and it puts me all out of.
You're sort of sick, that makes sense.
So why would do what I do instead of that if it's really quiet is I pay to
position.
And I just find that works so much better for me like it's worth trying it's
only like four or five credits and you can just go on position like put
yourself on a couple of minutes before the hour.
And for me I'd rather pay that for five credits, then sitting free for half an
hour because I find that's so draining and it just puts me a bad mood and it
makes me anxious and all the things you were just saying, it makes me exactly
the same.
Yeah.
I can't really agree.
Yeah, sorry.
I was just going to say I completely agree with what Sam you just said, and
what you said too about you feeling anxious about going on to free chat and
stuff.
I'm exactly the same way I can't.
Like, I just call some girls love it and like really do it so if you for
example she thinks she goes on it every time and she, she loves it and she goes
getting chat and stuff like that but personally for myself.
I just honestly I couldn't cope with it for more than 10 minutes because I
would just be like no like I'm logging off on this. So yeah, I mean you don't
have to do free chat and it might take, it might take a transition if you're
planning to use to seeing you know feature first.
It might be a bit of a transition period.
From being on it all the time to not being on it at all because your clients
might be like, oh well I was used to seeing it for free now or not, but you'll
just get new clients who are going to pay you trust me like some girls never
use free chat and still do really well.
And yeah, we'd be one of those girls is no reason why you can't be.
Probably agree I feel feel the same as well. I never do it very very rarely.
For me it's much better to spend my time updating a couple of things of a
profile put a picture on changing my tagline you know takes me 10 minutes and
bidding and just, and don't do free chat because it's like working for free isn
't it and if it doesn't come through you can be a bit just hard.
I've been in strip club for years and that's kind of like why I've stopped
doing that job because I just mentally couldn't do it anymore I just had like
nothing to give these men, and like, although I'm still obviously in sex with.
Like this is kind drawn my soul, and I can do it, you know in my own way on my
own terms like.
So I just feel like mentally a lot healthier come in now, and because take away
the lockdown situation because obviously I started then, which felt like it
wasn't my choice but like now it is.
Free chat. Yeah, it's been really draining for me.
I feel like thinking bigger than the situation you're now is just think that
you're a super successful person on there and that you don't need to do that
anymore.
Yeah.
Doing all the things that a successful person would do on there without doing
that.
You don't need that anymore.
Yeah, trust me it doesn't need to be done like I've been on that site for
almost 10 years.
I have never used free chat as in, I've turned on a few times just because I
have like we've having the agency and stuff like that's good for me to know,
you know how it works isn't there.
I've only ever used it for five or so minutes just to just to see how it works
and then I can ask if the girls ask me I can tell them.
I've never used it myself, never, and I've never had like, yeah, of course I
log on some days and I don't get many calls or whatever else.
So nearly 10 years I'm still in the industry and still able to make money from
this so if I can do it without free chat like we all can, you know what I mean.
It all can be done so trust me maybe working in the strip club maybe like it's
similar to obviously it's completely different because you're away from them.
But it's almost like the same with free chat like we can see you for free and
talk to you for free club, whereas, if you're just logging on and every time
you're they can see you're making money.
That's going to make you feel so much better again, you know, even more so so
in so yeah, my advice just turn it off put yourself on the front page.
And yeah, there could be a little bit of a transition period like I said if
they're used to seeing you for free and then all of a sudden they're not so
then it might you might lose people coming in the people that you still.
But then like I said earlier you're just making way for new people who are
going to pay you.
Yeah, yeah absolutely stunning and you're lovely girls so I'm sure you've got
no problems of with clients that are going to have to be a door yeah.
So yeah girl get on tonight and let us know you're going back on you said didn
't yeah so yeah I'm sure you'll smash it.
Yeah.
Yeah I'm going back on after this.
Amazing.
You look gorgeous like you could just log on right now you look stunning 100%.
No I love them.
You look so good.
Yeah, you do you look really innocent like oh.
I think I'm like a lot younger than I actually am on my other work profile.
That's in 100% you look gorgeous to slog on just go.
And maybe that's part of it as well that you don't need to make as like as much
effort as you can make it maybe.
It's awesome and you're doing loads of stuff maybe you can like that sometimes
you know in your class or whatever.
Yeah, maybe that maybe that's brings a different client.
And tell to know you a bit more and talk a bit longer.
Before you're going on is maybe thinking as well I've got to do this I've got
to do this I've got to put this off it.
Whereas if you're doing less like if you're not doing as many preparations you
just think you know what I'll give me so 15 minutes and I'll log on and just
get yourself on there.
I will actually go on like this like right now I don't have a strap and makeup
on and I would still go on like this.
Yeah I like it's nice to get done up in this and there, but also maybe that's
like adding to the stresses to you know and the anxiety.
But yeah.
So yeah I hope that advice helps and you'll have to keep those updates it's how
you're getting on without free chat and if you feel to turn it on every now and
again you know if you're a bit quiet and you feel like putting on then they're
great but don't feel like you have to do it every time and if it's
making you feel anxious and definitely don't do it.
Yeah, thank you.
I think I'm not going to do it tonight.
Yeah, maybe just try tonight without it and see how you get on.
Yeah, but I was recommending some page if you're not doing free chat.
If you've got a regular comment in then you know obviously that's great if you
know what time is coming, don't need to do from page then.
But if you've got credits to do from page I'd recommend going for it.
What's the time now it's eight o'clock so the next one will be nine.
From nine 10 on the day it starts to get get quite busy so um so yeah.
Good luck girl.
You love amazing.
Sure you'll do amazing.
Okay, anyone else want to share anything before we head off.
No, okay.
Okay then girly so thank you for coming along.
And yeah let's remember to get our one week goals done before Wednesday and
maybe we can all check in with each other on the chat and tell each other that
we got it done.
So yeah I hope you enjoy and we'll see you on the next call.
Thank you ladies.
Thank you George. Nice to see you all.
You're welcome.
Bye.
Bye darling baby baby.